- Okay, dig in.
- Hold up.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Bless us, O Lord, for these thy gifts
which we are about to receive...
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)...from thy bounty through Christ our Lord,
amen.
(Howard:)Took the words right out of my mouth.
(Bernadette:)So, Dad, have you done any fishing lately?
- I'm going next weekend.
- Oh. You like to fish?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Howard:)Sure. I can hear it in your voice.
(Mrs. Rostenkowski:)If he didn't like it, he wouldn't go.
(Howard:)You know, I hadn't thought of that.
(Howard:)Help me.
(Bernadette:)Dad, maybe you could take Howard
fishing sometime.
- Give you a chance to get to know each other.
- No, no. We know each other well enough.
(Howard:)He's been talking my ear off all night.